that to target specialty groups which have a higher propensity to want to test and treat.
So those are, of course, cardiovascular specialty groups, but also when you think about
interventional cardiology, I mean, there are certain specialty groups we're learning that
have a higher propensity to look for these biomarkers and then treat in order to avoid
the recurrence of events, also given the push towards healthcare quality around the world.
So we're trying to take a very targeted approach in how we think about our LP little a launch.
And in the future as well, in cardiovascular launches in general, take a more specialty
mindset which allows us to target to the right patients and the right physicians
with better resource allocation and hopefully drive more rapid uptake in the future.
Thank you, Richard.
Thank you.
Your next question comes from the line of Graham Parry, Bank of America.
Please go ahead.
Great.
Thanks for taking my questions.
Just wanted to come back to Natalie, actually.
Can you just clarify, you still think there's no manufacturing site inspection needed for
the new process?
I think you said on Q1 you didn't expect to see one.
I assume you'd actually know by now.
And just, again, that you remain confident that there is no adcom coming and confidence
in the broad label.
I know there's some discussion in the market about the node negative patient population
and whether that's approvable or not.
Thank you.
Yeah, thanks, Graham.
Again, based on the label discussions that we have, we're confident in the broad label
and there is no manufacturing inspection.
I mean, all of the changes we've made are all related to product handling.
And so I think, and some of the suppliers in the system.
So there's no inspections.
This is just providing stability data, which we're always obligated to do when we make
changes.
Once we finish, provide that stability data and have adequate stability data.
That's where the FDA takes their decision.
So it's really a topic of finalizing that review of our stability data from an FDA standpoint.
But we've put a little comment in the broad label, no other inspections.
And we're gearing up for a launch in late Q3.
Next question, operator.
Thank you.
Your next question comes from the line of James Quigley from Goldman Sachs.
Please go ahead.
Great.
Thank you for taking my questions.
I've got one on.
Could you walk us through some of the competitive dynamics you're seeing in the U.S.?
I mean, you mentioned some of the centers had 30% share.
So what is the considerations there in terms of driving the increase in share in those
centers?
And then thinking also about the community centers, where are you in terms of the development
of the community centers and Plovicto and the offering there?
And when you speak to docs, physicians in those centers, how are they thinking about
Plovicto, which is relatively more complicated than the androgen receptor inhibitors, which
are overall simple and seem to be launching quite strongly as well?
Thank you.
Yeah, thanks, James.
When you look at the dynamics on Plovicto, so we have, let's say, roughly 425 centers.
And about a third of those centers, we were really well established.
In the vision population, we see 90% market share, so really high levels of share of the
vision patients.
Then we have another group of centers, which are still earlier on in their evolution.
We see about 50% share.
Our goal is to get them to 90%.
The last third of centers are much more in the community.
And here, the dynamics are where we have to just do more work.
A lot of it is education.
So physicians understand, rather than cycling through, in the case of the vision population,
cycling through chemo and perhaps doing extra rounds of chemo, better to refer and have
the patients receive Plovicto, given the compelling results that we saw in the vision population.
So in order to motivate that, we're doing a few things, as I mentioned, another field
force to get out there to educate community oncology, community urology, and as well to
strengthen that referral base.
Second, DTC to make sure patients understand in the community that there is this option,
so rather than cycling through chemo.
Earlier on, where we know the earlier patients get Plovicto, the better the outcomes to
try to motivate that.
And I think if we can unlock that segment.
Over the course of the coming months, we can continue to drive Plovicto in the vision
population to the multi-billion or roughly $2 billion potential we think there is.
And that includes globally.
I would say we're seeing very robust uptake in Germany.
And over time, we expect robust uptake in other European markets.
Now, all of that is important for the current indication, but even more important as we
move to PSMA4, where we have three times the patient population.
And there, again, it will be.
It will be really important to, over time, build up confidence in the community to be
able, outside of the main medical centers, to provide radioligant therapy, not only for
Plovicto, but a portfolio of radioligant.
So we're confident we're going to get there step by step, but it will take time.
I think things like the patient-ready dose will help.
I think also.